var title = 'Traduza para grego.<br>Para substantivos, inclua o artigo definido (ο, η, το...).';

var questions = [

 {
   prompt: "a saúde",
   answer: ["η υγεία", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "inglês (a língua)",
   answer: ["τα αγγλικά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o basquete",
   answer: ["το μπάσκετ-μπωλ", "το μπάσκετμπολ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o amanhã",
   answer: ["το αύριο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o milagre",
   answer: ["το θαύμα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "(eu) trabalho",
   answer: ["δουλέυω", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o Euro (moeda)",
   answer: ["το Ευρώ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a palavra",
   answer: ["η λέξη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a terra",
   answer: ["η γη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a hora",
   answer: ["η ώρα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a imagem",
   answer: ["η εικόνα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a música",
   answer: ["η μουσική", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "as espécies",
   answer: ["τα είδη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a garagem",
   answer: ["το γκαράζ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "os átomos, os indivíduos",
   answer: ["τα άτομα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "as importações",
   answer: ["οι εισαγωγές", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "monótono",
   answer: ["μονότονος", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a vergonha",
   answer: ["η ντροπή", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o desastre",
   answer: ["η συμφορά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o comércio",
   answer: ["το εμπόριο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a benção",
   answer: ["η ευλογία", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o carro, automóvel",
   answer: ["το αυτοκίνητο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o amanhã",
   answer: ["το αύριο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a quinta-feira",
   answer: ["η Πέμπτη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a noite",
   answer: ["η νύχτα", "το βράδυ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o dia",
   answer: ["η μέρα", "η ημέρα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

];